Guide to the North Carolina State University, Athletics, Media Relations Records
North Carolina State University, Athletics, Media Relations Records
- Men's Basketball, 1911-2008; 1911 2008; The first official Men's Basketball game was played in 1911 against Wake Forest, and was held in the old Pullen Hall auditorium. In 1924, home games were moved from Raleigh Memorial Auditorium to the first on-campus facility: Thompson Gymnasium. With a 13-6 
  - "Controlled Fast Break," by Everette N. Case ( Athletic Jounal, Vol 37. No. 4), Dec. 1956 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Freshman Basketball game-by-game scoring, 1956-1957 (Legalbox 17, Folder 3)
  - Freshman Basketball questionnaires, 1956-1957 (Legalbox 17, Folder 4)
  - Media guide, 1956-1957 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Pre-season Men's Basketball press releases, 1956-1957 (Legalbox 17, Folder 10)
  - Men's Basketball press releases, Dec. 1956 (Legalbox 17, Folder 5)
  - Men's Basketball press releases, Jan. 1957 (Legalbox 17, Folder 6)
  - Men's Basketball press releases, Feb. 1957 (Legalbox 17, Folder 7)
  - Men's Basketball press releases, Mar. 1957 (Legalbox 17, Folder 8)
  - Player profiles and features, 1956-1957 (Legalbox 17, Folder 9)
  - Programs, 1956-1957 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Regular season basketball tickets, 1956-1957 (Legalbox 17, Folder 11)
  - Roster, 1956-1957 (Legalbox 17, Folder 12)
  - Roster, 1956-1957 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Schedule, 1956-1957 (Legalbox 17, Folder 13)
  - Statistics, 1956-1957 (Legalbox 17, Folder 14)
  - Statistics, 1956-1957 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Varsity Basketball questionnaires, 1956-1957 (Legalbox 17, Folder 15)
  - Freshman-Varsity game, 22 Oct. 1956 (Legalbox 17, Folder 16)
  - NC State vs. Pittsburgh, 1 Dec. 1956 (Legalbox 17, Folder 17)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest, 4 Dec. 1956 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - NC State vs. Penn State, 8 Dec. 1956 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - NC State vs. Clemson, 11 Dec. 1956 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - NC State vs. George Washington, 15 Dec. 1956 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - NC State vs. Eastern Kentucky, 17 Dec. 1956 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - NC State vs. La Salle, 20 Dec. 1956 (Legalbox 17, Folder 18)
  - NC State vs. West Virginia, 22 Dec. 1956 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Dixie Classic press releases, 1956 (Legalbox 17, Folder 19)
  - Dixie Classic program, 27-29 Dec. 1956 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Dixie Classic statistics, 27-29 Dec. 1956 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Dixie Classic ticket list, 1956 (Legalbox 17, Folder 20)
  - Dixie Classic, first day, 27 Dec. 1956 (Legalbox 17, Folder 21)
  - Dixie Classic: first day, 27 Dec. 1956 (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Dixie Classic: second day, 28 Dec. 1956 (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Dixie Classic: third day, 29 Dec. 1956 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - NC State vs. Duke, 5 Jan. 1957 (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - NC State vs. Florida State, 10 Jan. 1957 (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 15 Jan. 1957 (Legalbox 17, Folder 22)
  - NC State vs. Maryland, 19 Jan. 1957 (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - NC State vs. Fort Lee, 26 Jan. 1957 (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - NC State vs. Virginia, 29 Jan. 1957 (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - NC State vs. Clemson, 2 Feb. 1957 (Box 43, Folder 45)
  - NC State vs. Virginia, 5 Feb. 1957 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina, 9 Feb. 1957 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Duke, 12 Feb. 1957 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Maryland, 16 Feb. 1957 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 19 Feb. 1957 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Villanova, 23 Feb. 1957 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest, 2 Mar. 1957 (Legalbox 17, Folder 23)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament, 7-9 Mar. 1957 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament, UNC-Chapel Hill vs. South Carolina, 9 Mar. 1957 (Legalbox 17, Folder 24)
  - Box scores, 1957-1958 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Freshman Basketball game-by-game scoring, 1957-1958 (Legalbox 17, Folder 25)
  - Freshman Basketball questionnaires, 1957-1958 (Legalbox 17, Folder 26)
  - Media guide, 1957-1958 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Men's Basketball press releases, 1957-1958 (Legalbox 17, Folder 27)
  - Programs, 1957-1958 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Rosters, 1957-1958 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Schedule, 1957-1958 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Score book, 1957-1958 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Script for basketball highlight film, 1957 (Legalbox 17, Folder 28)
  - Statistics, 1957-1958 (Legalbox 18, Folder 1)
  - Statistics, 1957-1958 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Varsity Basketball questionnaires, 1957-1958 (Legalbox 18, Folder 2)
  - Harlem Globe Trotters at Reynolds Coliseum, 13 Nov. 1957 (Box 264, Folder 62)
  - NC State vs. Atlantic Christian, 2 Dec. 1957 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest, 5 Dec. 1957 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - NC State vs. Penn State, 7 Dec. 1957 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - NC State vs. Clemson, 10 Dec. 1957 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina, 11 Dec. 1957 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - NC State vs. Eastern Kentucky, 14 Dec. 1957 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - NC State vs. Villanova, 19 Dec. 1957 (Legalbox 18, Folder 3)
  - Dixie Classic press releases, 26-28 Dec. 1957 (Legalbox 18, Folder 4)
  - Dixie Classic program (2 copies), 26-28 Dec. 1957 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Dixie Classic ticket list, 1957 (Legalbox 18, Folder 5)
  - Dixie Classic visiting team press releases, 1957 (Legalbox 18, Folder 6)
  - Dixie Classic: first day, 26 Dec. 1957 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Dixie Classic: second day, 27 Dec. 1957 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Dixie Classic: third day, 28 Dec. 1957 (Legalbox 18, Folder 7)
  - Dixie Classic: third day, 28 Dec. 1957 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - NC State vs. Virginia, 1 Jan. 1958 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - NC State vs. Duke, 11 Jan. 1958 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 15 Jan. 1958 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - NC State vs. Maryland, 20 Jan. 1958 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - NC State vs. Clemson, 1 Feb. 1958 (Legalbox 18, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Virginia, 4 Feb. 1958 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina, 8 Feb. 1958 (Legalbox 18, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. Duke, 11 Feb. 1958 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - NC State vs. Maryland, 15 Feb. 1958 (Legalbox 18, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 18 Feb. 1958 (Legalbox 18, Folder 11)
  - NC State vs. La Salle, 22 Feb. 1958 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest, 1 Mar. 1958 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament press list, 1958 (Legalbox 18, Folder 13)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament program, 6-8 Mar. 1958 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament statistics, 6-8 Mar. 1958 (Legalbox 18, Folder 14)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament: first day, 6 Mar. 1958 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament: second day, 7 Mar. 1958 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament: third day, 8 Mar. 1958 (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - North-South Basketball Game, 28 Mar. 1958 (Legalbox 18, Folder 12)
  - Box scores, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Freshman Basketball questionnaire, 1958-1959 (Legalbox 18, Folder 15)
  - Freshman Basketball roster, 1958-1959 (Legalbox 18, Folder 16)
  - Media guide, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - Men's Basketball press releases, 1958-1959 (Legalbox 18, Folder 17)
  - Press, radio, television outlets, 1958-1959 (Legalbox 18, Folder 18)
  - Programs, 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - Schedule, 1958-1959 (Legalbox 18, Folder 19)
  - Score book (1 of 2), 1958-1959 (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - Score book (2 of 2), 1958-1959 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Statistics, 1958-1959 (Legalbox 18, Folder 20)
  - Statistics, 1958-1959 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Varsity Basketball questionnaires, 1958-1959 (Legalbox 18, Folder 21)
  - Varsity Basketball rosters, 1958-1959 (Legalbox 18, Folder 22)
  - Varsity-Freshman game, 27 Nov. 1958 (Legalbox 18, Folder 23)
  - NC State vs. Penn State, 1 Dec. 1958 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Maryland, 3 Dec. 1958 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest, 6 Dec. 1958 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Clemson, 9 Dec. 1958 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. La Salle, 17 Dec. 1958 (Legalbox 18, Folder 24)
  - NC State vs. Kansas State, 19 Dec. 1958 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Kansas, 20 Dec. 1958 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Dixie Classic press releases, Dec. 1958 (Legalbox 18, Folder 25)
  - Dixie Classic program, 29-31 Dec. 1958 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Dixie Classic score book, 29-31 Dec. 1958 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Dixie Classic: first day, 29 Dec. 1958 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Dixie Classic: second day, 30 Dec. 1958 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Dixie Classic: third day, 31 Dec. 1958 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - NC State vs. Virginia, 6 Jan. 1959 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - NC State vs. Duke, 10 Jan. 1959 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 14 Jan. 1959 (Legalbox 18, Folder 26)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest, 17 Jan. 1959 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina (North-South Double Header), 30 Jan. 1959 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - NC State vs. Clemson (North-South Double Header), 31 Jan. 1959 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - NC State vs. Virginia, 3 Feb. 1959 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina, 7 Feb. 1959 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - NC State vs. Duke, 10 Feb. 1959 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - NC State vs. Maryland, 14 Feb. 1959 (Legalbox 18, Folder 27)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 18 Feb. 1959 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - NC State vs. Villanova, 21 Feb. 1959 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - NC State vs. Eastern Kentucky, 28 Feb. 1959 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament: first day, 5 Mar. 1959 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament: second day, 6 Mar. 1959 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament: third day, 7 Mar. 1959 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - North-South All-Star Basketball Game, 28 Mar. 1959 (Legalbox 18, Folder 28)
  - Box scores, 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Freshman Basketball questionnaires, 1959-1960 (Legalbox 18, Folder 29)
  - Game-by-game scoring, Freshman and Varsity, 1959-1960 (Legalbox 18, Folder 30)
  - Media guide, 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Men's Basketball press releases, 1959-1960 (Legalbox 18, Folder 31)
  - Programs, 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Schedule, 1959-1960 (Legalbox 18, Folder 32)
  - Statistics, 1959-1960 (Legalbox 19, Folder 1)
  - William Neal Reynolds Coliseum basketball records, 1959 (Legalbox 19, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Penn State, 1 Dec. 1959 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest, 5 Dec. 1959 (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina, 8 Dec. 1959 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - NC State vs. Kansas State, 11 Dec. 1959 (Legalbox 19, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Kansas, 12 Dec. 1959 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - NC State vs. Villanova, 16 Dec. 1959 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - NC State vs. Georgia Tech, 19 Dec. 1959 (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - Dixie Classic general information, 28-30 Dec. 1959 (Legalbox 19, Folder 4)
  - Dixie Classic press releases, 1959-1960 (Legalbox 19, Folder 5)
  - Dixie Classic program (2 copies), 28-30 Dec. 1959 (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - Dixie Classic: visiting team information, 28-30 Dec. 1959 (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - Dixie Classic: first day, 28 Dec. 1959 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Dixie Classic: second day, 29 Dec. 1959 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Dixie Classic: third day, 30 Dec. 1959 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Virginia, 5 Jan. 1960 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Duke, 9 Jan. 1960 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 13 Jan. 1960 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest, 16 Jan. 1960 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Maryland, 18 Jan. 1960 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Eastern Kentucky, 23 Jan. 1960 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. Clemson, 30 Jan. 1960 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. Virginia, 2 Feb. 1960 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - NC State vs. Duke, 9 Feb. 1960 (Legalbox 19, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Maryland, 13 Feb. 1960 (Legalbox 19, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 17 Feb. 1960 (Legalbox 19, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina, 19 Feb. 1960 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - NC State vs. Clemson, 20 Feb. 1960 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - NC State vs. La Salle, 26 Feb. 1960 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament: general information, 3-5 Mar. 1960 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament: first day, 3 Mar. 1960 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament: second day, 4 Mar. 1960 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament: third day, 5 Mar. 1960 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Advertisement text, 1960-1961 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - All-Star teams, 1960-1961 (Legalbox 19, Folder 9)
  - Basketball network, 1960-1961 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Box scores, 1960-1961 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Clippings, 1960-1961 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Clippings and features, 1961 (Legalbox 19, Folder 10)
  - Everett Case scrapbook, 1960-1966 (Flatbox 248)
    Contains clippings about Case's retirement from NC State and his funeral in May 1966.
  - Freshman Basketball general information, 1960-1961 (Legalbox 19, Folder 11)
  - Freshman Basketball statistics, 1960-1961 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Freshman and Varsity game-by-game scoring, 1960-1961 (Legalbox 19, Folder 12)
  - Media guide, 1960-1961 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Pre-season clippings and features, 1960-1961 (Legalbox 19, Folder 13)
  - Programs (1 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Programs (2 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Questionnaires, 1960-1961 (Legalbox 19, Folder 14)
  - Radio, 1960-1961 (Legalbox 19, Folder 15)
  - Rosters, 1960-1961 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Schedule, 1960-1961 (Legalbox 19, Folder 16)
  - Score book, 1960-1961 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Statistics, 1960-1961 (Legalbox 19, Folder 17)
  - Statistics, box scores, 1960-1961 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Freshman-Varsity basketball game, 24 Nov. 1960 (Legalbox 19, Folder 18)
  - NC State vs. Southern Illinois, 1 Dec. 1960 (Legalbox 19, Folder 19)
  - NC State vs. George Washington, 3 Dec. 1960 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - NC State vs. Clemson, 6 Dec. 1960 (Legalbox 19, Folder 20)
  - NC State vs. The Citadel, 10 Dec. 1960 (Legalbox 19, Folder 21)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest, 14 Dec. 1960 (Legalbox 19, Folder 22)
  - NC State vs. Georgia Tech, 17 Dec. 1960 (Legalbox 19, Folder 23)
  - NC State vs. La Salle, 21 Dec. 1960 (Legalbox 19, Folder 24)
  - Dixie Classic clippings, 1960-1961 (Legalbox 102, Folder 6)
  - Dixie Classic general information, 29-31 Dec. 1960 (Legalbox 20, Folder 1)
  - Dixie Classic program (2 copies), 29-31 Dec. 1960 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Dixie Classic program material, Dec. 1960 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Dixie Classic: first day, 29 Dec. 1960 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Dixie Classic: second day, 30 Dec. 1960 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Dixie Classic: third day, 31 Dec. 1960 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Virginia, 3 Jan. 1961 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Duke, 7 Jan. 1961 (Legalbox 20, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest, 14 Jan. 1961 (Legalbox 20, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 18 Jan. 1961 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Maryland, 21 Jan. 1961 (Legalbox 20, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina, 28 Jan. 1961 (Legalbox 20, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Virginia, 31 Jan. 1961 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. West Virginia, 4 Feb. 1961 (Legalbox 20, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Duke, 7 Feb. 1961 (Legalbox 20, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Maryland, 13 Feb. 1961 (Legalbox 20, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 15 Feb. 1961 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Carolinas Double-header general information, 17-18 Feb. 1961 (Legalbox 20, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina (Carolinas Double Header), 18 Feb. 1961 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Villanova, 23 Feb. 1961 (Legalbox 20, Folder 10)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament, 2-4 Mar. 1961 (Legalbox 20, Folder 11)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament: radio, Mar. 1961 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament: first day, 2 Mar. 1961 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament: second day, 3 Mar. 1961 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament: third day, 4 Mar. 1961 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Basketball scandals, 1961-1962 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Box scores, 1961-1962 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, 1961-1962 (Legalbox 20, Folder 12)
  - Clippings: All-Star honors, 1961-1962 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Freshman Basketball general information, 1961-1962 (Legalbox 20, Folder 13)
  - Freshman Basketball questionnaires, 1961-1962 (Legalbox 20, Folder 14)
  - Freshman Basketball statistics, 1961-1962 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Freshman and Varsity game-by-game scoring, 1961-1962 (Legalbox 20, Folder 15)
  - Media guide, 1961-1962 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - "Old Wicker Chair" (NC State / Wake Forest rivalry trophy), 1961-1962 (Box 264, Folder 63)
  - Pre-season clippings, 1961-1962 (Legalbox 20, Folder 16)
  - Programs (1 of 2), 1961-1962 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Programs (2 of 2), 1961-1962 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Radio, 1961-1962 (Legalbox 20, Folder 17)
  - Rosters, 1961-1962 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Schedule, 1961-1962 (Legalbox 20, Folder 18)
  - Score book, 1961-1962 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Statistics, 1961-1962 (Legalbox 20, Folder 19)
  - Statistics, box scores, 1961-1962 (Legalbox 25, Folder 5)
  - Varsity Basketball questionnaires, 1961-1962 (Legalbox 20, Folder 20)
  - Freshman-Varsity game, 23 Nov. 1961 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Tennessee, 2 Dec. 1961 (Legalbox 21, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest, 5 Dec. 1961 (Legalbox 21, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Alumni, 9 Dec. 1961 (Legalbox 21, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Maryland, 21 Dec. 1961 (Legalbox 21, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Duke, 6 Jan. 1962 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina, 13 Jan. 1962 (Legalbox 21, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 17 Jan. 1962 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Maryland, 20 Jan. 1962 (Legalbox 21, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Clemson, 27 Jan. 1962 (Legalbox 21, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Virginia, 30 Jan. 1962 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. West Virginia, 3 Feb. 1962 (Legalbox 21, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Duke, 6 Feb. 1962 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Virginia, 7 Feb. 1962 (Legalbox 21, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 14 Feb. 1962 (Legalbox 21, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina (North-South Double Header), 16 Feb. 1962 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Clemson (North-South Double Header), 17 Feb. 1962 (Legalbox 21, Folder 11)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest, 21 Feb. 1962 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament general information, 1-3 Mar. 1962 (Legalbox 21, Folder 12)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament radio, 1-3 Mar. 1962 (Legalbox 21, Folder 13)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament: first day, 1 Mar. 1962 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament: second day, 2 Mar. 1962 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament: third day, 3 Mar. 1962 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Adevertising, 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Brochure information, 1962-1963 (Legalbox 21, Folder 14)
  - Clippings, 1962-1963 (Legalbox 21, Folder 15)
  - Freshman Basketball clippings, 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Freshman Basketball questionnaires, 1962-1963 (Legalbox 21, Folder 16)
  - Freshman Basketball roster, 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Freshman Basketball statistics, 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Game-by-game scoring, 1962-1963 (Legalbox 21, Folder 17)
  - General information, 1962-1963 (Legalbox 22, Folder 1)
  - Media guide, 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Pre-season clippings, 1962-1963 (Legalbox 22, Folder 2)
  - Programs (1 of 3), 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Programs (2 of 3), 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Programs (3 of 3), 1962-1963 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Questionnaires, 1962-1963 (Legalbox 22, Folder 3)
  - Radio, 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Score book, 1962-1963 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Statistics, 1962-1963 (Legalbox 22, Folder 4)
  - Statistics, box scores, 1962-1963 (Legalbox 25, Folder 6)
  - Varsity roster, 1962-1963 (Legalbox 22, Folder 5)
  - Wolfpack Sports Network and radio, 1962-1963 (Legalbox 22, Folder 6)
  - Freshman-Varsity game, 22 Nov. 1962 (Legalbox 22, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Alumni, 1 Dec. 1962 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Clemson, 3 Dec. 1962 (Legalbox 22, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest, 8 Dec. 1962 (Legalbox 22, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. Maryland, 11 Dec. 1962 (Legalbox 22, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. George Washington, 15 Dec. 1962 (Legalbox 22, Folder 11)
  - NC State vs. Georgia Tech, 19 Dec. 1962 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Cornell, 2 Jan. 1963 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Duke, 5 Jan. 1963 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Virginia, 9 Jan. 1963 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina, 12 Jan. 1963 (Legalbox 22, Folder 12)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 16 Jan. 1963 (Legalbox 22, Folder 13)
  - NC State vs. Maryland, 19 Jan. 1963 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. The Citadel, 26 Jan. 1963 (Legalbox 22, Folder 14)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest, 30 Jan. 1963 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Virginia, 2 Feb. 1963 (Legalbox 22, Folder 15)
  - NC State vs. Duke, 9 Feb. 1963 (Legalbox 22, Folder 16)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 12 Feb. 1963 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Carolinas Double-Header general information, 15-16 Feb. 1963 (Legalbox 22, Folder 17)
  - NC State vs. Clemson (Carolinas Double Header), 15 Feb. 1963 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. South Carolina (Carolinas Double Header), 16 Feb. 1963 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - NC State vs. Virginia Military Institute, 23 Feb. 1963 (Legalbox 22, Folder 18)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament general information, 28 Feb. - 2 Mar. 1963 (Legalbox 23, Folder 1)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament score book, 28 Feb. - 2 Mar. 1963 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament: first day, 28 Feb. 1963 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament: second day, 1 Mar. 1963 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament: third day, 2 Mar. 1963 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Basketball School for Boys (7th Annual), 2-21 Jun. 1963 (Box 264, Folder 64)
  - Clippings, 1963-1964 (Legalbox 23, Folder 2)
  - End of Dixie Classic, 1963-1965 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Freshman Basketball clippings, 1963-1964 (Legalbox 23, Folder 3)
  - Freshman Basketball score book, 1963-1964 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Freshman Basketball statistics, 1963-1964 (Legalbox 23, Folder 4)
  - Media guide, 1963-1964 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Programs, 1963-1964 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Questionnaires, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Statistics, 1963-1964 (Legalbox 23, Folder 5)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament program, 5-7 Mar. 1964 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - NCAA Tournament: Eastern Regional program, 13-14 Mar. 1964 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Basketball clippings, 1964-1965 (Legalbox 23, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Basketball scorebook, 1964-1965 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Freshman Basketball statistics, 1964-1965 (Legalbox 23, Folder 7)
  - Media guide, 1964-1965 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Programs, 1964-1965 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Statistics, 1964-1965 (Legalbox 23, Folder 8)
  - Varsity Basketball clippings, 1964-1965 (Legalbox 23, Folder 9)
  - Varsity Basketball score book, 1964-1965 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Varsity Basketball statistics, 1964-1965 (Legalbox 23, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 3 Feb. 1965 (Box 266, Folder 36)
  - NCAA Tournament: Eastern Regional clippings, 10-14 Mar. 1965 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Freshman Basketball clippings, 1965-1966 (Legalbox 23, Folder 11)
  - Freshman Basketball score book, 1965-1966 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Pre-season clippings, 1965-1966 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Media guide (2 copies), 1965-1966 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Score books (1 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Score book (2 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Season ticket booklet, 1965-1966 (Box 264, Folder 65)